<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Govt &#8211; S Online Mills</title>
	<atom:link href="https://s.online.mills.edu/tag/govt/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://s.online.mills.edu</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 10:21:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://s.online.mills.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/mails.png</url>
	<title>Govt &#8211; S Online Mills</title>
	<link>https://s.online.mills.edu</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The Netherlands government will give people free sunscreen</title>
		<link>https://s.online.mills.edu/the-netherlands-government-will-give-people-free-sunscreen/</link>
					<comments>https://s.online.mills.edu/the-netherlands-government-will-give-people-free-sunscreen/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admins]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 10:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cancer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Europe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Govt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Netherlands]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[treatment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://s.online.mills.edu/?p=14</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Skin cancer patients are increasing day by day in the European country Netherlands. The government of the country has a novel plan to reduce this number. The Netherlands government will provide free sunscreen to the people of the country. As a result, it is believed that the risk of skin cancer can be greatly reduced [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Skin cancer patients are increasing day by day in the European country Netherlands. The government of the country has a novel plan to reduce this number. The Netherlands government will provide free sunscreen to the people of the country. As a result, it is believed that the risk of skin cancer can be greatly reduced even if exposed to direct sunlight.</p>



<p>According to the official sources of the Netherlands, this summer, sunscreen will be distributed to the general public in all educational institutions, parks, sports centers, festivals etc. in the country.</p>



<p>The country&#8217;s government believes that the people of the Netherlands want to be guaranteed protection from direct sunlight. And for the purpose of ensuring this protection, efforts are being made to distribute sunscreen free of cost. One of the aims of this initiative is to ensure that no one is deprived of this protection due to economic reasons.</p>



<p>According to local media reports, a dermatologist of the country first brought forward such an initiative. According to him, sunscreen should be given to the common people to prevent skin cancer, just like sanitizers were given to common people during the Corona epidemic.</p>



<p>Jako Knape, a resort consultant in the Netherlands, said that children should use sunscreen from an early age. Then children will get used to it. Using sunscreen will become a habit.</p>



<p>Skin cancer has been rampant throughout Europe for two decades. This problem is especially evident in the countries of Central Europe where the temperature rises a lot in summer. Doctors blame direct exposure to the sun&#8217;s ultraviolet rays behind skin cancer.</p>



<p>Due to this cancer, the color of certain parts of the skin changes. In such situations, according to experts, sunscreen should not be considered a cosmetic in any way. Rather, it should be considered as an important supplement that protects the skin from cancer.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://s.online.mills.edu/the-netherlands-government-will-give-people-free-sunscreen/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
