<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>USA &#8211; S Online Mills</title>
	<atom:link href="https://s.online.mills.edu/tag/usa/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://s.online.mills.edu</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 11:39:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://s.online.mills.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/mails.png</url>
	<title>USA &#8211; S Online Mills</title>
	<link>https://s.online.mills.edu</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Europe’s ‘crazy’ tourism summer has already started. And it’s going to get much worse</title>
		<link>https://s.online.mills.edu/europes-crazy-tourism-summer-has-already-started-and-its-going-to-get-much-worse/</link>
					<comments>https://s.online.mills.edu/europes-crazy-tourism-summer-has-already-started-and-its-going-to-get-much-worse/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admins]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 11:39:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Europe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://s.online.mills.edu/?p=20</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Not since the 1970s has Steve Perillo, CEO and third-generation owner of New Jersey-based tour operator Perillo Tours, seen such a spike in travelers booking trips to Europe. The company, which is best known for its custom tours to Italy, usually sells about 80% of its capacity in a year, Perillo says. So far in 2023, [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Not since the 1970s has Steve Perillo, CEO and third-generation owner of New Jersey-based tour operator Perillo Tours, seen such a spike in travelers booking trips to Europe.</p>



<p>The company, which is best known for its custom tours to Italy, usually sells about 80% of its capacity in a year, Perillo says. So far in 2023, approximately 96% of the operator’s 500 annual departures, which also include Spain and Greece as destinations, are booked – and Perillo expects that figure to hit 100% within a few weeks, before the company starts marketing for its 2024 season.</p>



<p>For Perillo, hints of the blockbuster season ahead started appearing last fall, when the company offered a Black Friday discount of about 5%. “We should have charged more for Black Friday,” he jokes. “That’s when we noticed that [demand] was outrageous, and I called all my friends the night of Black Friday and said, ‘this is going to be crazy.’”</p>



<p>In many parts of Europe, the craziness is already well underway, as droves of Europe-bound tourists follow in the well-trodden footsteps of their 2022 predecessors in last season’s post-Covid lockdown surge.</p>



<p>According to travel insurance provider Allianz Partners, the number of Americans traveling to Europe this summer is expected to soar by 55% over last year’s figures – which were already a staggering 600% higher than in 2021. London, Paris, and Dublin topped the 2023 list of the 10 most popular destinations revealed by Allianz’s annual review; Rome, Reykjavik, Amsterdam, and Lisbon also made the top 10.</p>



<p>The European Travel Commission also forecasted strong demand for European vacations in 2023, with nearly half of all destinations on the continent expecting a return to more than 80% of 2019 numbers.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://s.online.mills.edu/europes-crazy-tourism-summer-has-already-started-and-its-going-to-get-much-worse/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
