<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Europe &#8211; S Online Mills</title>
	<atom:link href="https://s.online.mills.edu/tag/europe/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://s.online.mills.edu</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 11:39:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://s.online.mills.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/mails.png</url>
	<title>Europe &#8211; S Online Mills</title>
	<link>https://s.online.mills.edu</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Europe’s ‘crazy’ tourism summer has already started. And it’s going to get much worse</title>
		<link>https://s.online.mills.edu/europes-crazy-tourism-summer-has-already-started-and-its-going-to-get-much-worse/</link>
					<comments>https://s.online.mills.edu/europes-crazy-tourism-summer-has-already-started-and-its-going-to-get-much-worse/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admins]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 11:39:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Europe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://s.online.mills.edu/?p=20</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Not since the 1970s has Steve Perillo, CEO and third-generation owner of New Jersey-based tour operator Perillo Tours, seen such a spike in travelers booking trips to Europe. The company, which is best known for its custom tours to Italy, usually sells about 80% of its capacity in a year, Perillo says. So far in 2023, [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Not since the 1970s has Steve Perillo, CEO and third-generation owner of New Jersey-based tour operator Perillo Tours, seen such a spike in travelers booking trips to Europe.</p>



<p>The company, which is best known for its custom tours to Italy, usually sells about 80% of its capacity in a year, Perillo says. So far in 2023, approximately 96% of the operator’s 500 annual departures, which also include Spain and Greece as destinations, are booked – and Perillo expects that figure to hit 100% within a few weeks, before the company starts marketing for its 2024 season.</p>



<p>For Perillo, hints of the blockbuster season ahead started appearing last fall, when the company offered a Black Friday discount of about 5%. “We should have charged more for Black Friday,” he jokes. “That’s when we noticed that [demand] was outrageous, and I called all my friends the night of Black Friday and said, ‘this is going to be crazy.’”</p>



<p>In many parts of Europe, the craziness is already well underway, as droves of Europe-bound tourists follow in the well-trodden footsteps of their 2022 predecessors in last season’s post-Covid lockdown surge.</p>



<p>According to travel insurance provider Allianz Partners, the number of Americans traveling to Europe this summer is expected to soar by 55% over last year’s figures – which were already a staggering 600% higher than in 2021. London, Paris, and Dublin topped the 2023 list of the 10 most popular destinations revealed by Allianz’s annual review; Rome, Reykjavik, Amsterdam, and Lisbon also made the top 10.</p>



<p>The European Travel Commission also forecasted strong demand for European vacations in 2023, with nearly half of all destinations on the continent expecting a return to more than 80% of 2019 numbers.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://s.online.mills.edu/europes-crazy-tourism-summer-has-already-started-and-its-going-to-get-much-worse/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>In the village where women talk about everything</title>
		<link>https://s.online.mills.edu/in-the-village-where-women-talk-about-everything/</link>
					<comments>https://s.online.mills.edu/in-the-village-where-women-talk-about-everything/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admins]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 10:45:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Europe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Greece]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[woman]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://s.online.mills.edu/?p=17</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[&#8216;Here the words of the women do everything&#8217; &#8211; so says Rigopola Pablidis, singing the praises of the remote village on the island of Karapathos. It is home to one of Greece&#8217;s rare matriarchal communities. Publicis&#8217;s husband, Giannis, was sitting on a chair nearby, painting religious portraits. He nodded his head and agreed to his [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>&#8216;Here the words of the women do everything&#8217; &#8211; so says Rigopola Pablidis, singing the praises of the remote village on the island of Karapathos. It is home to one of Greece&#8217;s rare matriarchal communities.</p>



<p>Publicis&#8217;s husband, Giannis, was sitting on a chair nearby, painting religious portraits. He nodded his head and agreed to his wife&#8217;s words.</p>



<p>Publidis was sitting in his company wearing traditional clothes. She said with a smile, &#8216;My husband can do nothing without me. Can&#8217;t even file his tax return.&#8217;</p>



<p>Greece is largely a patriarchal society. In contrast, in the village of Olympos, women are at the helm of everything.</p>



<p>Isolated from the rest of the Dodecanese islands, this spectacular mountain village retains its centuries-old heritage. The inhabitants of this place have held on to their traditions even between the Ottoman Empire in the 16th century and the Italian rule in the 20th century. Olympos did not have a ramp until the 1980s.</p>



<p>Local historian Giorgos Sampanakis said some of the Byzantine-era traditions still survive. One of them is that the eldest daughter gets the mother&#8217;s property in the inheritance system.</p>



<p>Tailors by profession are also beneficiaries of this succession system. He inherited 700 olive trees from his mother.</p>



<p>&#8220;There was not enough property to divide among all the children in the family,&#8221; says Pablidis. And if We had left the inheritance to men, they would have wasted it.&#8217;</p>



<p>In Greece, it is customary for girls to live in their husband&#8217;s house after marriage. But in Olympos it is the other way around. After marriage, the husband has to stay in the wife&#8217;s house.</p>



<p>The matter of matriarchal tradition can also be observed in the matter of names. Sampanakis says, &#8216;Older girls use the first part of their grandmother&#8217;s name with their own name. Although the first part of the grandfather&#8217;s name appears to be used elsewhere in Greece.&#8217; He said, &#8216;Many women still use their mother&#8217;s surname, not their husband&#8217;s.&#8217;</p>



<p>Women&#8217;s empowerment at Olympus increased in the 1950s, when men began to go abroad for work. Most of them go to USA and European countries. In this, the responsibility of looking after the family and the institution falls on the wife and daughters.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://s.online.mills.edu/in-the-village-where-women-talk-about-everything/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Netherlands government will give people free sunscreen</title>
		<link>https://s.online.mills.edu/the-netherlands-government-will-give-people-free-sunscreen/</link>
					<comments>https://s.online.mills.edu/the-netherlands-government-will-give-people-free-sunscreen/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admins]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 10:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cancer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Europe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Govt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Netherlands]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[treatment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://s.online.mills.edu/?p=14</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Skin cancer patients are increasing day by day in the European country Netherlands. The government of the country has a novel plan to reduce this number. The Netherlands government will provide free sunscreen to the people of the country. As a result, it is believed that the risk of skin cancer can be greatly reduced [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Skin cancer patients are increasing day by day in the European country Netherlands. The government of the country has a novel plan to reduce this number. The Netherlands government will provide free sunscreen to the people of the country. As a result, it is believed that the risk of skin cancer can be greatly reduced even if exposed to direct sunlight.</p>



<p>According to the official sources of the Netherlands, this summer, sunscreen will be distributed to the general public in all educational institutions, parks, sports centers, festivals etc. in the country.</p>



<p>The country&#8217;s government believes that the people of the Netherlands want to be guaranteed protection from direct sunlight. And for the purpose of ensuring this protection, efforts are being made to distribute sunscreen free of cost. One of the aims of this initiative is to ensure that no one is deprived of this protection due to economic reasons.</p>



<p>According to local media reports, a dermatologist of the country first brought forward such an initiative. According to him, sunscreen should be given to the common people to prevent skin cancer, just like sanitizers were given to common people during the Corona epidemic.</p>



<p>Jako Knape, a resort consultant in the Netherlands, said that children should use sunscreen from an early age. Then children will get used to it. Using sunscreen will become a habit.</p>



<p>Skin cancer has been rampant throughout Europe for two decades. This problem is especially evident in the countries of Central Europe where the temperature rises a lot in summer. Doctors blame direct exposure to the sun&#8217;s ultraviolet rays behind skin cancer.</p>



<p>Due to this cancer, the color of certain parts of the skin changes. In such situations, according to experts, sunscreen should not be considered a cosmetic in any way. Rather, it should be considered as an important supplement that protects the skin from cancer.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://s.online.mills.edu/the-netherlands-government-will-give-people-free-sunscreen/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
