<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>UNESCO &#8211; S Online Mills</title>
	<atom:link href="https://s.online.mills.edu/tag/unesco/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://s.online.mills.edu</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 09:29:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://s.online.mills.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/mails.png</url>
	<title>UNESCO &#8211; S Online Mills</title>
	<link>https://s.online.mills.edu</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>How many shipwrecks are there at the bottom of the ocean?</title>
		<link>https://s.online.mills.edu/how-many-shipwrecks-are-there-at-the-bottom-of-the-ocean/</link>
					<comments>https://s.online.mills.edu/how-many-shipwrecks-are-there-at-the-bottom-of-the-ocean/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admins]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 09:29:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[The Ocean]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[The Ship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UNESCO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United Nations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://s.online.mills.edu/?p=8</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization (UNESCO) announced the discovery of three shipwrecks at the bottom of the sea recently. Two of the three newly discovered shipwrecks are thousands of years old. Now it is said, how many other shipwrecks can lie at the bottom of the sea? In 1900, a Roman shipwreck [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization (UNESCO) announced the discovery of three shipwrecks at the bottom of the sea recently.</p>



<p>Two of the three newly discovered shipwrecks are thousands of years old. Now it is said, how many other shipwrecks can lie at the bottom of the sea?</p>



<p>In 1900, a Roman shipwreck was discovered in the sea near the Greek island of Antikythera. The cargo ship sank more than two thousand years ago. Various ancient artefacts were recovered from the wreckage of the ship.</p>



<p>The ancient artefacts recovered from the wreck of the ship are housed in the museum. More than 100 years have passed since this artifact was recovered. Nevertheless, these signs continue to fascinate and amaze people.</p>



<p>Many more shipwrecks are believed to lie beneath the world&#8217;s oceans. They are still waiting to be discovered. If they are discovered, if various signs are recovered from them, it can be assumed that it will surprise people.</p>



<p>UNESCO recently conducted an expedition to the sea area known as &#8216;Skerky Bank&#8217;. It is also known as &#8216;Skerky Channel&#8217;. This dangerous waterway connects the Eastern and Western Mediterranean.</p>



<p>The waterway has been widely used for thousands of years. But hundreds of ships have sunk here during this long time.</p>



<p>Scientists-researchers from eight countries participated in the expedition conducted in the Skerky Bank area. The expedition uses the latest technology, including underwater robots.</p>



<p>At the end of the expedition, the discovery of three shipwrecks was announced. The three vessels are from the first century BC, the second century AD and the nineteenth or twentieth century.</p>



<p>According to UNESCO, many shipwrecks can still be found under the world&#8217;s oceans, which have never been found before.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Wrecks hidden in the sea</h2>



<p>An ancient boat was accidentally found on the seabed during the construction of a motorway in the Netherlands. The canoe is believed to be 10,000 years old.</p>



<p>Circumstantial evidence indicates that the waterways of this area began to be navigated long before 10,000 years ago.</p>



<p>It is believed that about 50,000 years ago, a group of hunters crossed the long sea route from Southeast Asia.</p>



<p>In seas where there is evidence of navigation, wrecks (ships) are presumed to exist.</p>



<p>Shipwrecks are now scattered under the oceans of the world. There are pirate ships loaded with silver, cargo ships or luxury royal ships. There are ancient fishing vessels, modern destroyers and submarines. The list includes 19th century whaling ships as well as giant passenger liners like the Titanic.</p>



<p>The shipwrecks that have been discovered so far have fascinated archaeologists. Artifacts recovered from these are enriching the museums of the world.</p>



<p>Such as the wreckage of a ship discovered near the island of Antikythera in Greece. A &#8216;mysterious&#8217; astronomy-related watch was recovered from here. The watch is considered by some experts to be the world&#8217;s first computer.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">How many ships are there in the sea?</h2>



<p>How many ships are lying under the sea-ocean? How many ships are still unknown?</p>



<p>There are several databases of shipwrecks in the world. However, the statistics on shipwrecks in each database differ.</p>



<p>One such online database is &#8216;Rake Site&#8217;. They claim to be the world&#8217;s largest database of A-related.</p>



<p>The Wreck site has information on 296,400 shipwrecks. Of these, 1 lakh 79 thousand 110 are known in the database.</p>



<p>On the other hand, the Global Maritime Wrecks Database contains information on more than 250,000 shipwrecks. Some of these vessels have not yet been found.</p>



<p>According to one estimate, around 15,000 ships were sunk during World War II alone. Many warships and tankers sunk from the Pacific to the Atlantic during this war are forgotten today.</p>



<p>The information that has been recorded so far about shipwrecks at sea cannot be called a complete picture at all. The data obtained is considered to be a small fraction of the actual number.</p>



<p>UNESCO has a convention on the protection of underwater cultural heritage. The Convention was adopted in 2001. According to a UNESCO analysis, there are more than 3 million undiscovered shipwrecks under the world&#8217;s oceans.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://s.online.mills.edu/how-many-shipwrecks-are-there-at-the-bottom-of-the-ocean/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
