<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>admins &#8211; S Online Mills</title>
	<atom:link href="https://s.online.mills.edu/author/admins/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://s.online.mills.edu</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 11:39:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://s.online.mills.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/mails.png</url>
	<title>admins &#8211; S Online Mills</title>
	<link>https://s.online.mills.edu</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Europe’s ‘crazy’ tourism summer has already started. And it’s going to get much worse</title>
		<link>https://s.online.mills.edu/europes-crazy-tourism-summer-has-already-started-and-its-going-to-get-much-worse/</link>
					<comments>https://s.online.mills.edu/europes-crazy-tourism-summer-has-already-started-and-its-going-to-get-much-worse/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admins]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 11:39:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Europe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://s.online.mills.edu/?p=20</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Not since the 1970s has Steve Perillo, CEO and third-generation owner of New Jersey-based tour operator Perillo Tours, seen such a spike in travelers booking trips to Europe. The company, which is best known for its custom tours to Italy, usually sells about 80% of its capacity in a year, Perillo says. So far in 2023, [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Not since the 1970s has Steve Perillo, CEO and third-generation owner of New Jersey-based tour operator Perillo Tours, seen such a spike in travelers booking trips to Europe.</p>



<p>The company, which is best known for its custom tours to Italy, usually sells about 80% of its capacity in a year, Perillo says. So far in 2023, approximately 96% of the operator’s 500 annual departures, which also include Spain and Greece as destinations, are booked – and Perillo expects that figure to hit 100% within a few weeks, before the company starts marketing for its 2024 season.</p>



<p>For Perillo, hints of the blockbuster season ahead started appearing last fall, when the company offered a Black Friday discount of about 5%. “We should have charged more for Black Friday,” he jokes. “That’s when we noticed that [demand] was outrageous, and I called all my friends the night of Black Friday and said, ‘this is going to be crazy.’”</p>



<p>In many parts of Europe, the craziness is already well underway, as droves of Europe-bound tourists follow in the well-trodden footsteps of their 2022 predecessors in last season’s post-Covid lockdown surge.</p>



<p>According to travel insurance provider Allianz Partners, the number of Americans traveling to Europe this summer is expected to soar by 55% over last year’s figures – which were already a staggering 600% higher than in 2021. London, Paris, and Dublin topped the 2023 list of the 10 most popular destinations revealed by Allianz’s annual review; Rome, Reykjavik, Amsterdam, and Lisbon also made the top 10.</p>



<p>The European Travel Commission also forecasted strong demand for European vacations in 2023, with nearly half of all destinations on the continent expecting a return to more than 80% of 2019 numbers.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://s.online.mills.edu/europes-crazy-tourism-summer-has-already-started-and-its-going-to-get-much-worse/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>In the village where women talk about everything</title>
		<link>https://s.online.mills.edu/in-the-village-where-women-talk-about-everything/</link>
					<comments>https://s.online.mills.edu/in-the-village-where-women-talk-about-everything/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admins]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 10:45:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Europe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Greece]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[woman]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://s.online.mills.edu/?p=17</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[&#8216;Here the words of the women do everything&#8217; &#8211; so says Rigopola Pablidis, singing the praises of the remote village on the island of Karapathos. It is home to one of Greece&#8217;s rare matriarchal communities. Publicis&#8217;s husband, Giannis, was sitting on a chair nearby, painting religious portraits. He nodded his head and agreed to his [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>&#8216;Here the words of the women do everything&#8217; &#8211; so says Rigopola Pablidis, singing the praises of the remote village on the island of Karapathos. It is home to one of Greece&#8217;s rare matriarchal communities.</p>



<p>Publicis&#8217;s husband, Giannis, was sitting on a chair nearby, painting religious portraits. He nodded his head and agreed to his wife&#8217;s words.</p>



<p>Publidis was sitting in his company wearing traditional clothes. She said with a smile, &#8216;My husband can do nothing without me. Can&#8217;t even file his tax return.&#8217;</p>



<p>Greece is largely a patriarchal society. In contrast, in the village of Olympos, women are at the helm of everything.</p>



<p>Isolated from the rest of the Dodecanese islands, this spectacular mountain village retains its centuries-old heritage. The inhabitants of this place have held on to their traditions even between the Ottoman Empire in the 16th century and the Italian rule in the 20th century. Olympos did not have a ramp until the 1980s.</p>



<p>Local historian Giorgos Sampanakis said some of the Byzantine-era traditions still survive. One of them is that the eldest daughter gets the mother&#8217;s property in the inheritance system.</p>



<p>Tailors by profession are also beneficiaries of this succession system. He inherited 700 olive trees from his mother.</p>



<p>&#8220;There was not enough property to divide among all the children in the family,&#8221; says Pablidis. And if We had left the inheritance to men, they would have wasted it.&#8217;</p>



<p>In Greece, it is customary for girls to live in their husband&#8217;s house after marriage. But in Olympos it is the other way around. After marriage, the husband has to stay in the wife&#8217;s house.</p>



<p>The matter of matriarchal tradition can also be observed in the matter of names. Sampanakis says, &#8216;Older girls use the first part of their grandmother&#8217;s name with their own name. Although the first part of the grandfather&#8217;s name appears to be used elsewhere in Greece.&#8217; He said, &#8216;Many women still use their mother&#8217;s surname, not their husband&#8217;s.&#8217;</p>



<p>Women&#8217;s empowerment at Olympus increased in the 1950s, when men began to go abroad for work. Most of them go to USA and European countries. In this, the responsibility of looking after the family and the institution falls on the wife and daughters.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://s.online.mills.edu/in-the-village-where-women-talk-about-everything/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Netherlands government will give people free sunscreen</title>
		<link>https://s.online.mills.edu/the-netherlands-government-will-give-people-free-sunscreen/</link>
					<comments>https://s.online.mills.edu/the-netherlands-government-will-give-people-free-sunscreen/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admins]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 10:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cancer]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Europe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Govt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Netherlands]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[treatment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://s.online.mills.edu/?p=14</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Skin cancer patients are increasing day by day in the European country Netherlands. The government of the country has a novel plan to reduce this number. The Netherlands government will provide free sunscreen to the people of the country. As a result, it is believed that the risk of skin cancer can be greatly reduced [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Skin cancer patients are increasing day by day in the European country Netherlands. The government of the country has a novel plan to reduce this number. The Netherlands government will provide free sunscreen to the people of the country. As a result, it is believed that the risk of skin cancer can be greatly reduced even if exposed to direct sunlight.</p>



<p>According to the official sources of the Netherlands, this summer, sunscreen will be distributed to the general public in all educational institutions, parks, sports centers, festivals etc. in the country.</p>



<p>The country&#8217;s government believes that the people of the Netherlands want to be guaranteed protection from direct sunlight. And for the purpose of ensuring this protection, efforts are being made to distribute sunscreen free of cost. One of the aims of this initiative is to ensure that no one is deprived of this protection due to economic reasons.</p>



<p>According to local media reports, a dermatologist of the country first brought forward such an initiative. According to him, sunscreen should be given to the common people to prevent skin cancer, just like sanitizers were given to common people during the Corona epidemic.</p>



<p>Jako Knape, a resort consultant in the Netherlands, said that children should use sunscreen from an early age. Then children will get used to it. Using sunscreen will become a habit.</p>



<p>Skin cancer has been rampant throughout Europe for two decades. This problem is especially evident in the countries of Central Europe where the temperature rises a lot in summer. Doctors blame direct exposure to the sun&#8217;s ultraviolet rays behind skin cancer.</p>



<p>Due to this cancer, the color of certain parts of the skin changes. In such situations, according to experts, sunscreen should not be considered a cosmetic in any way. Rather, it should be considered as an important supplement that protects the skin from cancer.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://s.online.mills.edu/the-netherlands-government-will-give-people-free-sunscreen/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sydney is like &#8216;Mayapuri&#8217; in the evening and night with the combination of light and sound.</title>
		<link>https://s.online.mills.edu/sydney-is-like-mayapuri-in-the-evening-and-night-with-the-combination-of-light-and-sound/</link>
					<comments>https://s.online.mills.edu/sydney-is-like-mayapuri-in-the-evening-and-night-with-the-combination-of-light-and-sound/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admins]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 09:33:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Australia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[festival]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sourced light]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://s.online.mills.edu/?p=11</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The weather in Sydney, Australia is cold now. Winter clothes should be worn even on sunny days. After the sunset, Sydney now becomes a &#8216;Mayapuri&#8217; in the winter evenings and nights. Sydney&#8217;s high-rises and famous buildings were suddenly flooded with light. A soft sound comes out. &#8216;Where did I come from?&#8217;- such a question arises [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The weather in Sydney, Australia is cold now. Winter clothes should be worn even on sunny days. After the sunset, Sydney now becomes a &#8216;Mayapuri&#8217; in the winter evenings and nights. Sydney&#8217;s high-rises and famous buildings were suddenly flooded with light. A soft sound comes out. &#8216;Where did I come from?&#8217;- such a question arises in the minds of newcomers to Sydney. Intoxicated with flashes of light and music, this festival is called &#8216;Vivid Sydney&#8217;.</p>



<p>&#8216;Vivid Sydney&#8217; is a mind-blowing 23-night festival of light and sound. There are many other things that accompany the festival. This festival started on May 26 and will continue till June 17.</p>



<p>Every year around the famous Sydney Opera House, Harbor Bridge, Botanic Gardens are decorated with colorful lights around the festival.</p>



<p>Exhibitions at this Sydney festival bring to life the works of over 200 photographers from over 25 countries.</p>



<p>Millions of visitors from different parts of the world flock to Sydney to see the convergence of art, technology and commerce. When the daylight disappears, the face in a different light suddenly makes the familiar Sydney unrecognizable.</p>



<p>Music is one of the parts of Alok Utsav. From the beginning of the festival, you can enjoy this music arrangement free of charge. This tune can be heard from any part of the main city.</p>



<p>For the first time, Vivid Sydney has added a bahari food festival. This is called &#8216;Vivid Food&#8217;.</p>



<p>Many cultural cuisines are closely associated with Sydney. Food has been added to this festival to introduce food from many countries.</p>



<p>The event includes fire-themed food, fusion food, live food prepared by celebrity chefs, floral food, gourmet food, self-made food. There is also a light fair on the food table during the festival.</p>



<p>This year&#8217;s Vivid Sydney festival attracted a record number of visitors in its first week. More than four and a half lakh visitors arrived in the first week of the festival.</p>



<p>About 2.1 million visitors came to see Vivid Sydney 2022 over 23 days. The light festival continues to play an important role in Sydney&#8217;s economy.</p>



<p>Bangladeshis living in Australia also watch this festival of Vivid Sydney.<br>Bangladeshi actor Ziaul Farooq Apurba and actress Sabila Noor are now staying in Sydney to shoot the drama. There is director Shihab Shaheen and his team.</p>



<p>Apurba came to see this one of the light festival in the world. About the experience of Vivid Sydney, he said, &#8216;Sydney is an amazingly beautiful city. In between, I came across a festival like Vivid Sydney, which is truly unparalleled. I have never seen such a scene before.&#8217;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://s.online.mills.edu/sydney-is-like-mayapuri-in-the-evening-and-night-with-the-combination-of-light-and-sound/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How many shipwrecks are there at the bottom of the ocean?</title>
		<link>https://s.online.mills.edu/how-many-shipwrecks-are-there-at-the-bottom-of-the-ocean/</link>
					<comments>https://s.online.mills.edu/how-many-shipwrecks-are-there-at-the-bottom-of-the-ocean/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admins]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 09:29:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[The Ocean]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[The Ship]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UNESCO]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United Nations]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://s.online.mills.edu/?p=8</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization (UNESCO) announced the discovery of three shipwrecks at the bottom of the sea recently. Two of the three newly discovered shipwrecks are thousands of years old. Now it is said, how many other shipwrecks can lie at the bottom of the sea? In 1900, a Roman shipwreck [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization (UNESCO) announced the discovery of three shipwrecks at the bottom of the sea recently.</p>



<p>Two of the three newly discovered shipwrecks are thousands of years old. Now it is said, how many other shipwrecks can lie at the bottom of the sea?</p>



<p>In 1900, a Roman shipwreck was discovered in the sea near the Greek island of Antikythera. The cargo ship sank more than two thousand years ago. Various ancient artefacts were recovered from the wreckage of the ship.</p>



<p>The ancient artefacts recovered from the wreck of the ship are housed in the museum. More than 100 years have passed since this artifact was recovered. Nevertheless, these signs continue to fascinate and amaze people.</p>



<p>Many more shipwrecks are believed to lie beneath the world&#8217;s oceans. They are still waiting to be discovered. If they are discovered, if various signs are recovered from them, it can be assumed that it will surprise people.</p>



<p>UNESCO recently conducted an expedition to the sea area known as &#8216;Skerky Bank&#8217;. It is also known as &#8216;Skerky Channel&#8217;. This dangerous waterway connects the Eastern and Western Mediterranean.</p>



<p>The waterway has been widely used for thousands of years. But hundreds of ships have sunk here during this long time.</p>



<p>Scientists-researchers from eight countries participated in the expedition conducted in the Skerky Bank area. The expedition uses the latest technology, including underwater robots.</p>



<p>At the end of the expedition, the discovery of three shipwrecks was announced. The three vessels are from the first century BC, the second century AD and the nineteenth or twentieth century.</p>



<p>According to UNESCO, many shipwrecks can still be found under the world&#8217;s oceans, which have never been found before.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Wrecks hidden in the sea</h2>



<p>An ancient boat was accidentally found on the seabed during the construction of a motorway in the Netherlands. The canoe is believed to be 10,000 years old.</p>



<p>Circumstantial evidence indicates that the waterways of this area began to be navigated long before 10,000 years ago.</p>



<p>It is believed that about 50,000 years ago, a group of hunters crossed the long sea route from Southeast Asia.</p>



<p>In seas where there is evidence of navigation, wrecks (ships) are presumed to exist.</p>



<p>Shipwrecks are now scattered under the oceans of the world. There are pirate ships loaded with silver, cargo ships or luxury royal ships. There are ancient fishing vessels, modern destroyers and submarines. The list includes 19th century whaling ships as well as giant passenger liners like the Titanic.</p>



<p>The shipwrecks that have been discovered so far have fascinated archaeologists. Artifacts recovered from these are enriching the museums of the world.</p>



<p>Such as the wreckage of a ship discovered near the island of Antikythera in Greece. A &#8216;mysterious&#8217; astronomy-related watch was recovered from here. The watch is considered by some experts to be the world&#8217;s first computer.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">How many ships are there in the sea?</h2>



<p>How many ships are lying under the sea-ocean? How many ships are still unknown?</p>



<p>There are several databases of shipwrecks in the world. However, the statistics on shipwrecks in each database differ.</p>



<p>One such online database is &#8216;Rake Site&#8217;. They claim to be the world&#8217;s largest database of A-related.</p>



<p>The Wreck site has information on 296,400 shipwrecks. Of these, 1 lakh 79 thousand 110 are known in the database.</p>



<p>On the other hand, the Global Maritime Wrecks Database contains information on more than 250,000 shipwrecks. Some of these vessels have not yet been found.</p>



<p>According to one estimate, around 15,000 ships were sunk during World War II alone. Many warships and tankers sunk from the Pacific to the Atlantic during this war are forgotten today.</p>



<p>The information that has been recorded so far about shipwrecks at sea cannot be called a complete picture at all. The data obtained is considered to be a small fraction of the actual number.</p>



<p>UNESCO has a convention on the protection of underwater cultural heritage. The Convention was adopted in 2001. According to a UNESCO analysis, there are more than 3 million undiscovered shipwrecks under the world&#8217;s oceans.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://s.online.mills.edu/how-many-shipwrecks-are-there-at-the-bottom-of-the-ocean/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
