<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Australia &#8211; S Online Mills</title>
	<atom:link href="https://s.online.mills.edu/tag/australia/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://s.online.mills.edu</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 09:33:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://s.online.mills.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/mails.png</url>
	<title>Australia &#8211; S Online Mills</title>
	<link>https://s.online.mills.edu</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Sydney is like &#8216;Mayapuri&#8217; in the evening and night with the combination of light and sound.</title>
		<link>https://s.online.mills.edu/sydney-is-like-mayapuri-in-the-evening-and-night-with-the-combination-of-light-and-sound/</link>
					<comments>https://s.online.mills.edu/sydney-is-like-mayapuri-in-the-evening-and-night-with-the-combination-of-light-and-sound/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admins]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 09:33:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Australia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[festival]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sourced light]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://s.online.mills.edu/?p=11</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The weather in Sydney, Australia is cold now. Winter clothes should be worn even on sunny days. After the sunset, Sydney now becomes a &#8216;Mayapuri&#8217; in the winter evenings and nights. Sydney&#8217;s high-rises and famous buildings were suddenly flooded with light. A soft sound comes out. &#8216;Where did I come from?&#8217;- such a question arises [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The weather in Sydney, Australia is cold now. Winter clothes should be worn even on sunny days. After the sunset, Sydney now becomes a &#8216;Mayapuri&#8217; in the winter evenings and nights. Sydney&#8217;s high-rises and famous buildings were suddenly flooded with light. A soft sound comes out. &#8216;Where did I come from?&#8217;- such a question arises in the minds of newcomers to Sydney. Intoxicated with flashes of light and music, this festival is called &#8216;Vivid Sydney&#8217;.</p>



<p>&#8216;Vivid Sydney&#8217; is a mind-blowing 23-night festival of light and sound. There are many other things that accompany the festival. This festival started on May 26 and will continue till June 17.</p>



<p>Every year around the famous Sydney Opera House, Harbor Bridge, Botanic Gardens are decorated with colorful lights around the festival.</p>



<p>Exhibitions at this Sydney festival bring to life the works of over 200 photographers from over 25 countries.</p>



<p>Millions of visitors from different parts of the world flock to Sydney to see the convergence of art, technology and commerce. When the daylight disappears, the face in a different light suddenly makes the familiar Sydney unrecognizable.</p>



<p>Music is one of the parts of Alok Utsav. From the beginning of the festival, you can enjoy this music arrangement free of charge. This tune can be heard from any part of the main city.</p>



<p>For the first time, Vivid Sydney has added a bahari food festival. This is called &#8216;Vivid Food&#8217;.</p>



<p>Many cultural cuisines are closely associated with Sydney. Food has been added to this festival to introduce food from many countries.</p>



<p>The event includes fire-themed food, fusion food, live food prepared by celebrity chefs, floral food, gourmet food, self-made food. There is also a light fair on the food table during the festival.</p>



<p>This year&#8217;s Vivid Sydney festival attracted a record number of visitors in its first week. More than four and a half lakh visitors arrived in the first week of the festival.</p>



<p>About 2.1 million visitors came to see Vivid Sydney 2022 over 23 days. The light festival continues to play an important role in Sydney&#8217;s economy.</p>



<p>Bangladeshis living in Australia also watch this festival of Vivid Sydney.<br>Bangladeshi actor Ziaul Farooq Apurba and actress Sabila Noor are now staying in Sydney to shoot the drama. There is director Shihab Shaheen and his team.</p>



<p>Apurba came to see this one of the light festival in the world. About the experience of Vivid Sydney, he said, &#8216;Sydney is an amazingly beautiful city. In between, I came across a festival like Vivid Sydney, which is truly unparalleled. I have never seen such a scene before.&#8217;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://s.online.mills.edu/sydney-is-like-mayapuri-in-the-evening-and-night-with-the-combination-of-light-and-sound/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
