<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Greece &#8211; S Online Mills</title>
	<atom:link href="https://s.online.mills.edu/tag/greece/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://s.online.mills.edu</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 10:45:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://s.online.mills.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/mails.png</url>
	<title>Greece &#8211; S Online Mills</title>
	<link>https://s.online.mills.edu</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>In the village where women talk about everything</title>
		<link>https://s.online.mills.edu/in-the-village-where-women-talk-about-everything/</link>
					<comments>https://s.online.mills.edu/in-the-village-where-women-talk-about-everything/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admins]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 10:45:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[World]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Europe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Greece]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[woman]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://s.online.mills.edu/?p=17</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[&#8216;Here the words of the women do everything&#8217; &#8211; so says Rigopola Pablidis, singing the praises of the remote village on the island of Karapathos. It is home to one of Greece&#8217;s rare matriarchal communities. Publicis&#8217;s husband, Giannis, was sitting on a chair nearby, painting religious portraits. He nodded his head and agreed to his [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>&#8216;Here the words of the women do everything&#8217; &#8211; so says Rigopola Pablidis, singing the praises of the remote village on the island of Karapathos. It is home to one of Greece&#8217;s rare matriarchal communities.</p>



<p>Publicis&#8217;s husband, Giannis, was sitting on a chair nearby, painting religious portraits. He nodded his head and agreed to his wife&#8217;s words.</p>



<p>Publidis was sitting in his company wearing traditional clothes. She said with a smile, &#8216;My husband can do nothing without me. Can&#8217;t even file his tax return.&#8217;</p>



<p>Greece is largely a patriarchal society. In contrast, in the village of Olympos, women are at the helm of everything.</p>



<p>Isolated from the rest of the Dodecanese islands, this spectacular mountain village retains its centuries-old heritage. The inhabitants of this place have held on to their traditions even between the Ottoman Empire in the 16th century and the Italian rule in the 20th century. Olympos did not have a ramp until the 1980s.</p>



<p>Local historian Giorgos Sampanakis said some of the Byzantine-era traditions still survive. One of them is that the eldest daughter gets the mother&#8217;s property in the inheritance system.</p>



<p>Tailors by profession are also beneficiaries of this succession system. He inherited 700 olive trees from his mother.</p>



<p>&#8220;There was not enough property to divide among all the children in the family,&#8221; says Pablidis. And if We had left the inheritance to men, they would have wasted it.&#8217;</p>



<p>In Greece, it is customary for girls to live in their husband&#8217;s house after marriage. But in Olympos it is the other way around. After marriage, the husband has to stay in the wife&#8217;s house.</p>



<p>The matter of matriarchal tradition can also be observed in the matter of names. Sampanakis says, &#8216;Older girls use the first part of their grandmother&#8217;s name with their own name. Although the first part of the grandfather&#8217;s name appears to be used elsewhere in Greece.&#8217; He said, &#8216;Many women still use their mother&#8217;s surname, not their husband&#8217;s.&#8217;</p>



<p>Women&#8217;s empowerment at Olympus increased in the 1950s, when men began to go abroad for work. Most of them go to USA and European countries. In this, the responsibility of looking after the family and the institution falls on the wife and daughters.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://s.online.mills.edu/in-the-village-where-women-talk-about-everything/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
